# Anez Escandon



### CONTACT

**Phone** 830-352-7507

*E-mail* iescan4@gmail.com

Address
3106 Holly Hall St.
Houston, TX
77054

### **LINKS**

GitHub Profile

https://github.com/iescandon

Portfolio

https://iescandon.github.io/

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/iescandon/

# **LANGUAGES**

English

Spanish

### **OBJECTIVE**

Looking to leverage ten years experience as an educator to quickly learn and grow in a web development career. Because of her professionalism and strong work ethic, she has been put into leadership roles and been asked to mentor other teachers. As an educator, she has proved her strong organizational/communication skills and ability to effectively multitask/manage challenging tasks all while achieving the goals in a fast-paced work environment. A highly motivated self-starter who is fully committed to proving herself in a new career, she would be a great asset to any company.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Physical Education Teacher, Deer Park ISD

Pasadena, TX (Aug 2017 - Aug 2020)

Bilingual Teacher, Deer Park ISD Pasadena, TX (Aug 2014 - Aug 2017)

Instructional Technology Specialist, Sheldon ISD Sheldon, TX (Aug 2013 - Aug 2014)

**Dual Language Teacher, North East ISD**San Antonio, TX (Aug 2010 - Aug 2013)

### **SKILLS**

### Technical Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap CSS
- Materialize CSS
- Javascript
- JSON
- jQuery
- AJAX
- Web APIs
- Node.js
- UI/UX Design

### **Additional Skills**

- Leadership/Takes Initiative
- Strong Problem Solving Abilities
- Ability to Work in a Team/Adaptable
- High Attention to Detail
- Effective Communication
- Energetic Work Attitude
- Creative and Innovative Thinking
- Quick Learner

# **EDUCATION**

University of Texas at Austin

Austin, TX (May 2010) Bachelors in Bilingual Education

University of Texas at San Antonio

San Antonio, TX (May 2013) Masters in Instructional Technology